

GAME PROGRAMMER

Details

Gdańsk

Poland

grzpotry@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Polish

DATE OF BIRTH

1995

Links

Github

Skills

Unity / C#

Unreal Engine / C++

Continous Integration (Jenkins/TeamCity)

Languages

Polish

English

Hobbies

Science, Astrophysics, Outdoor, Scuba-Diving, Hiking, Videography, Triathlon, Sci-Fi

Profile

Software Engineer and Game Developer since 2016.

Having extensive experience in a rapidly growing studio, evolving from a small self-funded startup to a mid-sized company. This progression required wearing many hats and engaging in various phases of the development process, from conceptualization to the final releases.

I thrive when tackling new challenges, with a wealth of experience in transforming design concepts into gameplay, I am consistently focused on optimizing workflows efficiency and innovation.

Employment History

Unity Programmer - Tower of Time, Event Horizon

MAY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

https://store.steampowered.com/app/617480/Tower_of_Time/

Tower of Time was first project in game dev I've worked on in newly emerging game studio Event Horizon. During that time I was still studying on University so it was part-time job mostly. I was chiefly responsible for gameplay programming and tools in small team of 4 programmers.

Senior Unity Programmer - Dark Envoy, Event Horizon

OCTOBER 2019 - JANUARY 2024

https://store.steampowered.com/app/945770/Dark_Envoy/

After successful launch of Tower of Time, we work on more ambitious RPG title with multiplayer co-op, procedural content generation, cinematic in-game cutscenes, voice over and much deeper rpg progression mechanics.

Technical areas in which i participated the most:

- Procedural Content Generation
- Al behavior trees & tools
- Tools to enhance designers workflow, 3rd party tools integration and maintance
- Combat & quest gameplay mechanics
- CI (Jenkins) automated builds and tests
- CPU optimizations

Unreal Engine Programmer - Survive the Fall, Angry Bulls Studio

OCTOBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Small part-time order at the early stage of Survive the Fall development.

Unreal Engine Programmer - Unannounced Project, Event Horizon

FEBRUARY 2024 - PRESENT

Currently I work on unannounced action RPG in Unreal Engine 5 heavily based on Lyra and GAS (C++ and blueprints) with automation shifted from Jenkins to TeamCity.

Education

Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Gdańsk University of Technology

OCTOBER 2014 - FEBRUARY 2018